Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
(Susan:)Dad,
this is Sheldon's mother, Mary.
How do you do?
Nice to meet you.
And, of course, Mom.
Hello, my hateful shrew.
Hello to you,
you wrinkled old bastard.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Just got an e-mail
from the U.S. Air Force.
I'm just afraid if I respond,
then they'll know I got it.
Dude, the minute you opened that
e-mail, they knew you got it.
I mean, they're probably
looking at you
through the camera
right now.
Oh, God.
I think someone's
following us.
Uh, turn left here
and see if he turns with us.
Why is he turning here?
The restaurant's the other way.
(Howard:)I don't know.
He uses that traffic app.
Maybe there's an accident.
Oh, so follow him.
Oh, no!
Leonard, if you don't mind,
I think I'm a little tired.
I'm gonna call it a night.
Sure, Dad.
I'm a little
tuckered out myself.
Well, I will see you
all in the morning.
Would you like to share a cab?
That would be fine.
Where are you staying?
I'm at the Westin.